(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
常闇トワ 生誕祭 2025
重々重大発表あり!!
Tokoyami Towa Birthday Festival 2025
Super serious announcement!!
路地裏の真ん中で 慣れない景色と 少ない匂いに
In the middle of a back alley, amid unfamiliar sights and faint scents,
ヨワネハキ 作詞・作曲: 和ぬか
Yowunaki / Lyrics & Composition: Wanuka
私は終わるまで 染まっていくんでしょう
I will probably keep being dyed until it's over.
私は怖がりで 知らないことには 手を付けず
I'm a coward; I won't touch things I don't know.
誰かがやって来て 毒見をするまで 待っていた
I waited for someone to come and taste the poison first.
知ることは単純で マニュアル通りの 生活を
Learning is simple; leading a life according to the manual,
来る日も淡々と 過ごしていた
I've been spending my days indifferently.
そうや さあ さあ 昨日も私もこうだった
That's right, come on, come on, yesterday I was like this too.
そうや さあ さあ
That's right, come on, come on.
弱い音を吐いてる 薄っぺらい人間です
I'm a shallow human who utters weak sounds.
一歩前に出るのは やめときます 絡まれたくないからさ
I'll refrain from taking a step forward because I don't want to get involved.
描いた理想像に 現実味がないから
Because the ideal image I painted isn't realistic,
近づけないよう 生きておきます 明日も同じを 過ごしておきます
I'll live so as not to get close to it, and spend tomorrow the same way.
路地裏の真ん中で いつもの夕日を 薄目で眺めて
In the middle of a back alley, gazing at the usual sunset with narrowed eyes,
胸の中で呟いた いつまで続くんだろう
I whispered in my heart, 'I wonder how long this will last.'
そうや さあ さあ 昨日も夕飯これだった
That's right, come on, come on, yesterday's dinner was this too.
そうや さあ さあ
That's right, come on, come on.
自虐で切りが悪い 惨めな人間です
I'm a miserable human, unending in my self-deprecation.
一歩後ろに下がって 逃げときます 目立ちたくなんかないからさ
I'll take a step back and run away, because I don't want to stand out at all.
描いた理想像に 現実味がないから
Because the ideal image I painted isn't realistic,
近づけないよう 生きておきます 明日も同じを 過ごしておきます
I'll live so as not to get close to it, and spend tomorrow the same way.
弱い音を吐いてる 薄っぺらい人間です
I'm a shallow human who utters weak sounds.
一歩前に出るのは やめときます 絡まれたくないからさ
I'll refrain from taking a step forward because I don't want to get involved.
溜息ばっかついて 突き足りないの
I do nothing but sigh, yet it's never enough.
きっとそう上手くは いかないけどさ 試しにちょっと 生きてみよう
It surely won't go that smoothly, but let's try living a little.
鉄の弾が 正義の証明 貫けば 英雄に近づいた
Iron bullets are proof of justice. If they pierce through, I've come closer to being a hero.
悪魔の子 作詞・作曲: ヒグチアイ
Akuma no Ko / Lyrics & Composition: Higuchi Ai
その目を閉じて 触れてみれば
If I close my eyes and try to touch it...
同じ形 同じ体温の悪魔
Devils of the same shape and the same body temperature.
僕はダメで あいつはいいの？
Am I no good and they're okay?
そこに壁があっただけなのに
When there was simply a wall there.
生まれてしまった 運命嘆くな
Don't lament the fate of being born.
僕らはみんな
Because we are all
自由なんだから
Free.
鳥のように 羽があれば
If I had wings like a bird,
どこへだって 行けるけど
I could go anywhere.
帰る場所が なければ
But if I have no place to return to,
きっとどこへも行けない
I surely can't go anywhere.
ただただ生きるのは嫌だ
I don't want to just exist.
世界は残酷だ
The world is cruel.
それでも君を愛すよ
Even so, I will love you.
なにを犠牲にしても
No matter what I have to sacrifice.
それでも君を守るよ
Even so, I will protect you.
間違いだとしても 疑ったりしない
Even if it's a mistake, I won't doubt it.
正しさとは自分のこと 強く信じることだ
Righteousness is to believe strongly in oneself.
鉄の雨が降り頻る情景 テレビの中 映画に見えたんだ
The scene of iron rain falling incessantly; it looked like a movie on TV.
戦争なんて愚かな凶暴 関係ない 知らない国の話
War is such foolish brutality; it's an irrelevant story of a country I don't know.
それならなんで あいつ憎んで 黒い気持ち 隠しきれない理由
Then why do I hate them? The reason I can't hide these dark feelings.
説明だってできやしないんだ 僕らはなんて矛盾ばっかなんだ
I can't even explain it; we are just full of contradictions.
この言葉も訳されれば 本当の意味は伝わらない
Even if these words are translated, the true meaning won't be conveyed.
信じるのはその目を開いて 触れた世界だけ
All I believe in is the world I saw and touched with my own eyes.
ただただ生きるのは嫌だ
I don't want to just exist.
世界は残酷だ
The world is cruel.
それでも君を愛すよ
Even so, I will love you.
なにを犠牲にしても
No matter what I have to sacrifice.
それでも君を守るよ
Even so, I will protect you.
選んだ人の影 捨てたものの屍
The shadows of those chosen, the corpses of those cast aside.
気づいたんだ 自分の中 育つのは悪魔の子
I realized that what's growing inside of me is a child of evil.
正義の裏 犠牲の中 心には悪魔の子
Behind justice, amidst sacrifice, there is a child of evil in my heart.
そっと振り返って 奇跡どうしたって光って
Looking back softly, the miracle shines no matter what.
ありふれて君が いつだってスーパーヒーロー
Though it's common, you are always a superhero.
いつもポンコツだった私 止めなくて 未完成
I've always been a klutz, don't stop me, I'm incomplete.
アヒルの子はアヒルのまま 飛べないなんてさ
Saying that an ugly duckling stays a duckling and can't fly.
正しさなんて放っておいて 君となんかちょっと似ていて
Leaving righteousness aside, I'm somewhat similar to you.
凸凹だからジャストに噛み合うパズルピース
Puzzle pieces that fit just right because they're uneven.
繋げたい 繋げたい 届かない言葉も
I want to connect, I want to connect even the words that won't reach.
いつかは誰かの何かに なりたいから
Because someday I want to become something to someone.
Crazy, Noisy, 夢の中
Crazy, noisy, in a dream.
夢を見せて
Show me a dream.
Always going!
何千回 何万回 膝をついても
No matter how many thousands or tens of thousands of times I fall on my knees.
最大限 アイラブユーで立ち上がれるから
I can stand up with a maximum 'I love you'.
とびきりのサンキュー 消えないハッピーも勇気も
An extraordinary 'thank you', for the happiness and courage that won't fade.
...塗り潰しちゃって
...Paint over it all.
大失敗も後悔さえ愛せるなら
If I can love even my greatest failures and regrets,
背中には君という羽
I'll have wings known as "you" on my back.
チックタック追い越して いつもどこか乾いた焦燥感
Overtaking the tick-tock, always feeling a parched sense of impatience.
隣で走る君と 織りなすレゾナンスストーリー
A resonance story woven together with you running beside me.
君の色が私を塗り替えて
Your colors repaint me,
壊れかけの音で響くから
Because they resonate with a half-broken sound.
お伽話の続きをまだ描きたいんだよ
I still want to draw the continuation of the fairy tale.
連れて行くよ
I'll take you with me.
(Vocalizing)
Always going
何全回何万回迷い込んでも
No matter how many thousands or tens of thousands of times I get lost,
最大級 I love you な君がいるから
Because I have you, whom I love to the maximum degree.
本日スペシャルな Thank you さぁ手を持って
A special "Thank you" for today, now take my hand.
運命も手繰り寄せて
And pull even destiny towards us.
もうバイバイも涙も忘れないよ
I won't forget the goodbyes or the tears anymore.
止められなかった私のこの背中には
On this back of mine that couldn't be stopped,
君という羽
Are wings known as "you."
描いた未来の景色がここにある
The scenery of the future I drew is right here.
弱さも抱きしめていくから
Because I'll keep embracing even my weaknesses.
広げた翼が輝いていく
The wings I've spread are starting to shine.
旅立て明日
Set out for tomorrow.
等身大の私を映してたい ただ
I just want to reflect my true self.
望む瞬間衝動になってんだ くだらないとさ
The moment I desire it, it becomes an impulse. They say it's trivial.
曇りきっていく目をして
With eyes that are becoming completely clouded,
可能性だって夢を見てみたいのに
I want to try and see the dream of possibilities.
ずっとわかっていたんだけど 言葉は浮いてる対象に
I've known it all along, but words are just floating targets.
大袈裟だって思ってるんでしょ
You think I'm exaggerating, don't you?
ずっと黙っていたんだけど 心ってやっぱ正直だ
I've been keeping quiet, but the heart is honest after all.
打ち明けたい訳、感じ気がしてる
I feel like I have a reason to confide.
ここだよ響かせて
I'm right here, make it resonate.
掲げた鼓動で 描くの... 終わらないでしょう
Drawing with the heartbeat I've held up... it won't end, right?
灯になっていく
It's becoming a light.
何度も奪われ繰り返し 意志の傷痕に
Repeatedly robbed, on the scars of my will,
誓った
I made a vow.
失敗後悔は泣いて溜息の音がしてる
Failures and regrets are crying, making the sound of a sigh.
現状に不満はない 飲み込んだ気でいたんだ
I have no complaints with the status quo. I thought I'd swallowed it all.
泡、忘れないように
So as not to forget the fleeting bubbles,
降臨祭 もう汚されないように
Advent festival, so that I won't be tainted anymore.
もっと笑っていたいんだもん 大人になっていく代償に
Because I want to smile more, as a price for becoming an adult.
あなただってきっと思ってるんでしょ
You're probably thinking the same thing, aren't you?
ちゃんと分かっていたんだけど 心ってやっぱ正直だ
I understood it well, but the heart is honest after all.
失せなくなった痛みを 感じ気がしてる
I feel the pain that won't go away.
照らされたこの場所で
In this place that's lit up,
咲かせた手ほら 描くの... 終わらないでしょう
Look at the hand I've made bloom, drawing... it won't end, right?
我儘待っている
Selfishness is waiting.
取り戻した
I regained it
日々の傷跡に
in the scars of everyday life
誓った
I swore
心よ響かせて
Let my heart resonate
心を響かせて
ずっと
forever
心だよ響かせて
It's my heart, let it resonate
掲げたこの腕
This arm I raised
Never mind でしょ？
Never mind, right?
右に左に 繋がっていく
Connecting right and left
何度も
Over and over again
奪われたって 取り返した
Even if it's taken away, I'll take it back
日々の傷跡に
in the scars of everyday life
誓った
I swore
あっ、はい！　はぁ……
Ah, yes! *sigh*...
皆さん！
Everyone!
というわけで、本日は……えー
And so, today...
常闇トワ生誕祭2025にお越しくださりありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming to Tokoyami Towa's Birthday Festival 2025!
こんやっぴー！　ホロライブ4期生の常闇トワ様です！
Kon-yappi! It's Hololive 4th Gen's Tokoyami Towa-sama!
イェーイ！
Yay!
はぁ……ちょっと水飲んでもいいですか？
Haa... Can I drink some water?
水もらっていいですか？　すみません。
Can I have some water? Excuse me.
たららら……ちょっと。あっ、すみませんね。
Ta-ra-ra-ra... Just a bit. Ah, excuse me.
水。あっ、すごい。どこに行ってもカメラがね、映んのよね。
Water. Oh, wow. No matter where I go, the camera follows me.
はぁ……
Haa...
水おいしい。
Water is delicious.
ということで、皆さん！
So, everyone!
今日はライブにお越しいただきありがとうございます。
Thank you for coming to the live today.
3Dライブをやらさせていただいております。
I'm performing a 3D live.
ということで……えー、早速なんですけれども……
And so... uh, without further ado...
ありがとう、みんな。おめでとう、ありがとう。
Thank you, everyone. "Congratulations", thank you.
ありがとう！
Thank you!
見えてますよー。
I can see you!
はい、早速なんですけれどもね。
Yes, moving right along.
今回の配信のハッシュタグはこちら！
The hashtag for this stream is this!
#常闇トワ生誕祭2025 ということでね。
#TokoyamiTowaBirthdayFestival2025.
こちらね、Xでたくさんポストをしていただければなと思います。
I hope you'll post a lot on X using this.
スクリーンショットとかね、感想もいっぱいいただけたら嬉しいです。
I'd be happy if you could share screenshots and your thoughts.
スクショはね、もしかして、えー、素敵なのがあったら……
About the screenshots, if there are any nice ones...
ちょっとパク……パクリというか、拝借というか、
I might "steal"... not steal, but borrow...
何て言うんですかね、はい。
What should I call it? Yeah.
あのー、勝手に「これ使っちゃおう」みたいな感じで使って、
Like, just choosing one and saying "I'll use this",
これ終わった後にポストするかもしれないんですけども。
I might post them after this is over.
そのために撮っといてくれたらなーみたいな。
So I'd appreciate it if you could take some for that.
あの、手伝ってくれたらなーと思います。
I hope you can help me out.
よろしくお願いいたします。
Thank you very much.
フレームワークの共有ね！
Sharing frameworks!
言い方ね。フレームワークの共有だから。
That's the way to put it. It's sharing frameworks.
そしてね、本日はライブだけじゃなくて、
And today, it's not just the live,
いろんなね、発表もしたいと思いますので。
there are also various announcements to be made.
最後まで見ていてくれれば嬉しいです！
I'd be glad if you could watch until the end!
はい！
Yes!
ここまでなんですけれども、
Up until now...
1曲目にね、wanna-k-aさんの楽曲の「ヨワネハキ」。
The first song was "Yowanehaki" by wanna-k-a.
2曲目に、樋口アイさんの「悪魔の子」。
The second song was "Akuma no Ko" by Higuchi Ai.
え、そしてトワのオリジナル曲の「STY」と、
And then Towa's original songs, "STY" and...
「Present Day」を歌わせていただきました！
I sang "Present Day"!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
今日のね、配信のオープニングは、
The opening for today's stream...
「Present Day」のインストを使ってます！
I used the instrumental for "Present Day"!
テンション上がるよね！
It gets you pumped up, doesn't it?
はい、この曲かっこいい。
Yes, this song is cool.
かっこいいけど入りが難しいんで、
It's cool, but the timing for the start is hard,
いつも、あの、皆さんに聞こえないとこでクリックを振ってもらってます。
so I always have a click track playing where you can't hear it.
恥ずかしいんですけども、すごい難しいから。
It's a bit embarrassing, but it's really difficult.
はい。
Yes.
そしてね。
And then.
今日はね、ちょっと盛りだくさんに……情報が盛りだくさんなんだけど、
Today is a bit packed... the info is packed,
歌もね、皆さんに、お届けしたいと思いますので、
but I also want to deliver songs to everyone,
1回ここでちょっと落ち着いて。
so let me take a breather here for a moment.
次の曲にね、行きたいと思います。
I'd like to move on to the next song.
いっぱいね、発表がしたいと思うので。
I have a lot of announcements to make.
本当に待っててください。
So please, stay tuned.
はい！
Yes!
ということで、次の曲。
And so, the next song.
オリジナル楽曲続きになります。
It'll be another original song.
聴いてください。「My Abyss」。
Please listen. "My Abyss".
沈んでいく　de-value
Sinking, de-value
忘れて　混じり合う　Who am I?
Forgetting, blending together, who am I?
這い寄る　この気持ちはもう
Creeping in, this feeling is already...
溶けて消えていく
Melting and disappearing
絡まった導火線には　火を放ち近づけ　Pray
Light the tangled fuse and draw near, Pray
朽ちていた輪廻
The decayed cycle of rebirth
輪郭には 近近づけて
To the outline, getting closer
あなたは Dostat
You are Dostat
I wanna be a dancer
今宵溶け合うまで踊りましょう
Let's dance until we melt together tonight
目が合うのは誰？
Whose eyes am I meeting?
深い闇へ落ちていく
Falling into the deep darkness
手伸ばせ あなたまで
Reach out your hand, until I reach you
届きますように Climax 光射す
I hope it reaches you, Climax, light shines
先まで あなたの手を掴めるように I will
forward, so I can grab your hand, I will
光射す先には
Ahead where the light shines
どこまでも広がる The Abyss
The Abyss spreads infinitely
彷徨っていた In the backroom
I was wandering in the backroom
でも欲しいんだ Moon
But I still want it, the Moon
止まらぬ Greed or feeder
Unstoppable Greed or feeder
全部手に入れ Everything else
Grab everything, Everything else
Hey, this is the underground
悪っぽいヤツらばかりの夜
A night full of devilish characters
我慢しなくてもいいんじゃない？ もうこっちにおいで
You don't have to hold back, do you? Now, come over here
滴り落ちた目の傷を 手に握ったら Make you evil
If you hold the dripping eye scar in your hand, it'll make you evil
火照った背に触れて 近近づけて
Touch the flushed back, getting closer
あなたは Dostat
You are Dostat
I wanna be my master
今宵全て忘れて Welcome to my paradise
Forget everything tonight, Welcome to my paradise
La la la 沈んでゆく La la la 奪流
La la la sinking away, La la la swirling away
La la la 忘れて 交じり合う Who am I
La la la forgetting, blending together, Who am I
迷い寄る この気持ちはもう...
Wandering closer, this feeling is already...
Loop loop 絡まった
Loop loop, entangled
どこへ行こうか 近近づけて
where shall we go, getting closer
近づけて
getting closer
あなたは Dostat
You are Dostat
I wanna be yourself
今宵溶け合うまで踊りましょう
Let's dance until we melt together tonight
目が合うのは誰？
Whose eyes am I meeting?
深い闇へ落ちていく
Falling into the deep darkness
駆け出して この闇から
Run out from this darkness
逃げ出せるように Climax
so you can escape, Climax
光射す先まで
Ahead where the light shines
あなたの手を掴めたから I will
Since I was able to grab your hand, I will
光射す先には どこまでも広がる
Ahead where the light shines, it spreads infinitely
The Abyss どこまでも深く
The Abyss, infinitely deep
どこまでも続いていく The Abyss
The Abyss continues on forever
落ちていく
Falling away
バズビバザザ
作詞・作曲・編曲：てにをは
Buzz Be Bazar
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Teniwoha
昔々悪魔の娘が 顔のない国に作ったとさ
Once upon a time, a devil's daughter created a faceless country.
やがて多くの人々が集い 賑わった
Soon many people gathered and it became lively.
娘はいたく喜び 受け入れたが 顔のない人々は
The daughter was greatly pleased and accepted them, but the faceless people...
自ら神を名乗り始めた
...began to call themselves gods.
Talk to, talk to devil, talk to talk
顔のない神様の言う通り 供物は迷い子達の邪気
Just as the faceless gods say, the offerings are the malice of lost children
あれが欲しい これが欲しい 暴れては駄々こねる
I want that, I want this, raging and throwing tantrums
バズビバザブ そろそろ 分からせていこう
Buzz Be Bazar, it's about time to make them understand
瞬く間に あっちゅう間に 悪魔に びるびる悪魔に
In the blink of an eye, in no time, a devil, a quivering devil
瞬く間に あっちゅう間に 悪魔に あくまで悪魔に
In the blink of an eye, in no time, a devil, strictly a devil
強烈な洗礼浴びせ 奇跡をご覧あれ
Giving a intense baptism, behold the miracle
Buzz B, Buzz B, over!
滑稽にクラクラするほど 色付くは 何これ 邪魔だから
Comically dizzying, it turns colorful, what's this? It's in the way
絡みついた邪魔なモノ 外しちゃお 真っ向から 歌い踊る
Let's remove the entangled nuisances, singing and dancing head-on
当たり障り
Harmlessly
やばくない？ 混ざってない？ 声合わせ 唱えましょう
Isn't it crazy? Aren't they mixed? Let's raise our voices and chant
バズビバザブ Super God Stage Time
Buzz Be Bazar, Super God Stage Time
深くファナティック
Deeply fanatic
下手なロマンティック
Poorly romantic
出来だとかのサンキューです
Thank you for the results and all
個人的な感想とか
Personal thoughts and such
一方的な妄想とか
One-sided delusions and such
マジ終わってるんですけど
Seriously, you're hopeless
Whisper
ちょっと変身
A little transformation
もっと手招いて あつまれ悪魔に
Beckon more, gather for the devil
みるみる悪魔に
Rapidly becoming a devil
もっと手招いて あつまれ悪魔に
Beckon more, gather for the devil
あくまで悪魔に
To the end, as a devil
Guilty Guilty
Stupid Majesty
Bazzby Bazzby
Order
反吐が出ちゃう ぐるぐるセオリー
Nauseating, spinning theory
甘い神話 万有引力なら
A sweet myth, if it's universal gravitation
ここが聖地
Then this is the holy land
私に集え集え 相図は666
Gather to me, gather to me, the signal is 666
よろしく！ 物怖じして巻いてんじゃない
Regards! Don't be afraid and wrap it up
昔100もの娘が あの街に作ったとさ
Long ago, a hundred girls built it in that town
やがて多くの人々が集い 賑わった
Eventually, many people gathered and it became lively
真っ赤な 歌い踊る
Deep red, singing and dancing
寄ったり寄ったり これってヤバくない？
Getting closer and closer, isn't this crazy?
怖くない 声合わせて唱えましょう
Don't be afraid, let's chant together
バズビバザザ
Bazzby Buzzer
響かせよう
Let it ring out
セイ・コー・カウントダウン
Say ho, countdown
はい！ということで皆さん！
Okay! So, everyone!
常闇トワ、2ndアルバム「SHIN」の発表が...
Tokoyami Towa's 2nd album 'SHIN' announcement...
...発表じゃねぇわ、発売が決定しましたー！
...not announcement, the release has been decided!
はい！ありがとうございます！
Yes! Thank you very much!
お待たせしました！
Sorry to have kept you waiting!
はい、今回のジャケット写真は、秋面秋良さんに描き下ろしていただきました！
Yes, the jacket illustration for this time was newly drawn by Akizura Hanzawa!
めっちゃかっこいいでしょう、これ！
Isn't this so cool?!
鎖引きちぎってね、SHINなんだって！
Tearing apart the chains, it's 'SHIN'!
話そう！
Let's talk!
はい、そしてね、10月8日！トワの日ですね！
Yes, and then, October 8th! It's Towa's Day!
こちら、指定、設定させていただきました！
I have designated and set it to this date!
10月8日から、今回も1stに続き、全国流通での発売となっております！
From October 8th, following the 1st, it will be available for nationwide distribution!
はい、ありがとうございます！豪華作家陣の皆様に描き下ろしていただいた新曲が...
Yes, thank you! Many new songs newly written by a magnificent lineup of composers...
...たくさん収録されております！
...are included!
ジャケットいいでしょう！
The jacket is good, isn't it?!
もっと言って！もうすごい素敵なね、ジャケット書いてくれました。本当に嬉しいです！
Say more! They really drew such a wonderful jacket for me. I'm so happy!
そしてね、2ndアルバムなんですけれども、完全生産限定盤と通常盤の2種類をご用意しております。
And about the 2nd album, we have two types available: a Limited Edition and a Standard Edition.
まず、完全生産限定盤はこちら！
First, here is the Limited Edition!
じゃーん！あ、こっちだった。
Ta-da! Oh, it was over here.
外箱がね、超豪華スリーブボックスになっております！
The outer case is a super luxurious sleeve box!
ヘイ！ヘイ！だって、はい。彼方描いて、ヘイ！
Hey! Hey! because... yeah. Drawing the beyond, hey!
そして中身はこちら！
And here is the content!
アクリルブロックキーホルダーや、アナザージャケットカード、サイン入りオリジナルグッズなどが当たる...
An acrylic block keychain, another jacket card, and signed original goods that you can win...
...抽選応募券、6種類のMVカットステッカーセット！
...a lottery application ticket, and a set of 6 MV cut stickers!
あとはですね、ホロライブオフィシャルカードゲームPRカードの常闇トワなどなど...
And also, a Hololive Official Card Game PR card of Tokoyami Towa, and so on...
...豪華特典がたくさん入っております！
...many luxurious bonuses are included!
ボックスなんですけれどもね、通常のCDよりも、ちょっと一回り二回りぐらい大きい...
As for the box, it's about one or two sizes larger than a normal CD...
...本当に限定盤の、その、飾る用といういうか、そういう感じの...
...it's really like a limited edition thing, for display or something like that...
...プレミアム感がついた感じになっております！
...it has a premium feel to it!
…ような、え、ボックスの、え、限定版となっております。
...um, it's a limited edition box like this.
はい、そしてね、アナザージャケットカードにはランダムでトワのね、直筆サインが入っております。
Yes, and the Another Jacket Cards randomly include my handwritten signature.
はい、え、そしてね、プレゼントキャンペーン商品のラインナップはこちらです。ボーン！
Yes, and here is the lineup for the gift campaign prizes. Bam!
はい、このね、キービジュアル…ジャケ写？ジャケ写か。ジャケット写真を使った、
Yes, using this key visual... the jacket photo? Yeah, jacket photo. Using that photo,
Tシャツとか、ポスターとか、缶バッジがね、えー、できてます。かっこいいでしょ？
we've made T-shirts, posters, and button badges. Cool, right?
はい。かっこいいの欲しいよね！トワも、トワも欲しい。ごめんけど。
Yes. You want the cool ones, don't you? I want them too. Sorry!
だから、トワがじゃあ1枚取るから、2名さまと9名さまと…嘘ですよ嘘嘘。皆さんのためにちゃんとありますから。
So, I'll take one, and for 2 people, 9 people... Just kidding! There's enough for everyone.
はい、そしてね、続いて通常版はこちらです！ボーン！
Yes, and next, here is the Regular Edition! Bam!
はい、顔のね、ちょっとアップがボーンって入ったような。かっこいい、もう。目、もう釘付けでしょ、トワの顔に。はい。
Yes, with a big close-up of my face. So cool. Your eyes are glued to my face, right? Yes.
こちらのね、デザインとなっておりまして、通常版にはスマホサイズのジャケットイラストステッカーが入っております。
This is the design, and the Regular Edition includes a smartphone-sized jacket illustration sticker.
こちらのね、かっこいいジャケ写の、えー、ステッカー、スマホに貼ったり、PCに貼ったり、何ですか？
You can stick this cool jacket photo sticker on your smartphone, PC, or what else?
レバーレスとかに貼ったり、アケコンに貼ったりとかしてもらえれば嬉しいです。はい。
I'd be happy if you stuck it on your leverless controller or arcade stick. Yes.
そしてね、えー、こちら！今回のアルバムに楽曲を書き下ろしてくださった作家陣の皆様はこちらです。ボーン！
And then, this! Here are the creators who wrote new songs for this album. Bam!
実はね、さっき『ヨワネハキ』だとか『悪魔の子』だとか歌ってるけど、なんと書いてくれてるんですよ！書き下ろしてもらいました！
Actually, I sang 'Yowanehaki' and 'Akuma no Ko' earlier, and they actually wrote new songs for me!
実は伏線だったっていうね。はい、ちょっとそういう感じでちょっと組ませていただきました。いえーい！
It was actually foreshadowing. Yes, I had it set up like that. Yay!
はい。そうなんですよ。あとね、まあいろいろ、見てびっくりすることもあると思うんですけども。
Yes. That's right. Also, I think there might be some things that will surprise you when you see them.
あ、この前の『My Abyss』が収録されてたりとか、『バズビーバザブ』があったりとかしております。はい。
Ah, 'My Abyss' from the other day is included, and there's also 'Busby Bazab'. Yes.
どの楽曲もすごい素敵なしあがりなんで、楽しみにしていいてもらえればと思います。はい。
Every song turned out really wonderful, so I hope you look forward to them. Yes.
そして、各店舗別の特典はこちら！ボーン！もういろんな種類がいっぱいあるからね！
And here are the bonuses for each store! Bam! There are so many different types!
もうどの特典も欲しくなると思うんですけども。全部買ってもよし！選んで買ってもよし！ということで。
I think you'll want all of them. You can buy them all or pick and choose! So...
ひとつひとつ紹介したいところ、これを全部紹介するとたぶん5年ぐらい経つんで、自分で見てください、トワ。
I'd like to introduce them one by one, but it would take 5 years, so please check them yourself.
完全生産限定版も通常版も、絶対に手に入れてくださいと。そしてこちら、本日21時から発売開始なんですが…
Please make sure to get both the Limited and Regular Editions. These go on sale at 9 PM today...
が、が、が！ホロライブ公式ECでは、なんとこの配信中に…
But, but, but! On the Hololive official store, amazingly, during this stream...
（咳払い）なんですが！なんとホロライブ公式ECでは…編集点。配信中にCDが買えるようになるかも！
(Clears throat) But! On the Hololive official store... edit point. You might be able to buy the CD during the stream!
なんか出てきてポチって押せたりするか、ボーン。ということで楽しみに待っててください。はい。
Something might pop up for you to click, bam! So please look forward to it. Yes.
このあとですね、そして、次の曲はなんとこのあと、セカンドアルバムから1曲、新曲を披露します。
After this, for the next song, I'm going to perform a new track from my second album.
えー、nqrseさん、GTAとかでお世話になっているなるせ兄貴に、書き下ろしていただきました。『chewy chewy』という楽曲になります。
nqrse-san, who I know from GTA, wrote this for me. It's a song called 'chewy chewy'.
はい、この新曲『chewy chewy』はですね、この配信のあとにMVが8時50分からプレミア公開、24時に先行リリース予定です。
The MV for 'chewy chewy' premieres at 8:50 PM after this stream, and it releases at midnight.
やっぱね、nqrseさんと言ったらラップじゃないですか！ラップがあるのかどうかは、このあと歌いますから楽しみに！
When you think of nqrse-san, it's gotta be rap! As for the rap, I'm singing it now, so look forward to it!
MVに関しては、普段やったことない動きを、ディレクターさんに指示されながら、試行錯誤して頑張ってやったんで。
For the MV, I tried moves I don't usually do. I worked hard on it with the director's guidance.
ちょっと違和感もあるかもしれないけど頑張ったトワが見れる、スタイリッシュなMVに仕上がりました。
It might feel a bit different, but it's a stylish MV where you can see my hard work.
なのでプレミア公開は楽しみにしておいてください。そして、nqrseさんが書き下ろしてくれた『chewy chewy』を歌います。
So please look forward to the premiere. And now, I'll sing 'chewy chewy', written by nqrse-san.
ぜひ、えー、ちょっとここで落ち着かないとね。ぜひ、えー、聞いてもらえればと思います。では、『chewy chewy』！
Please, uh, I need to calm down first. Please listen to it. Well then, 'chewy chewy'!
Jitter bug no boy, lemon no boy, mimic shi no ghost ghost bash toh hai
Jitter bug boy, lemon boy, mimicking ghost ghost, bash, party time
Karana gaudo, kabishunogaudo, hariotoshi tojito irasuwaresugo
Empty guard, pretentious guard, needle drop, closing, erase, let's go
Mata senpi to jou de shibatteyo
Bind me again with whirlpools and locks
はずの今日を 好きなんだって
Saying you like today as it should be
不公平な 友情だって 期待したって
Even if it's an unfair friendship, even if I expect it
No pain, No gain
どのハートも 毒仕掛け
Every heart is a poison trap
任された 毒手になって
Becoming the entrusted poison hand
ジュースはもう 消し去っていいよ
You can erase the juice now
甘い音 包む幻想
Sweet sounds, an enveloping illusion
囚われるのに 救えない
Imprisoned, yet unable to be saved
水のように 透き通った 溜め息
A sigh as transparent as water
Don't see your side in the memory
忘れてた事も
Even the things I'd forgotten
忘れてきた白夜闇 頭に響く足音
The midnight sun's darkness I've forgotten, footsteps echoing in my head
迷いもなく 振り向かない
Without hesitation, I won't look back
Tell me many many more... wow
Chewy Chewy
くだらないって 笑って 惑わせて
Call it worthless, laugh, and lead me astray
有象無象 風に吹かれ 目に打たれ Fade out
The masses blown by the wind, struck in the eyes, Fade out
今日と明日を 描いて
Drawing today and tomorrow
くだらたって 始まりね 火を灯せ
Even if it's worthless, it's a beginning, light the fire
Hello, Hello 差し舞って 疑って お好きの
Hello, Hello, offer a dance, doubt it, just as you like
Trust me... Hook up baby
Chewy Chew, Chewy Chew
Mogu mogu mogu Chewy Chew, Chewy Chew
手を合わせ何度も カッ飛ばしてしまった迷路
Joining hands, time and again, I've dashed through the maze
騙されたまま いたいわ
I want to remain deceived
退屈なのは 正解は
Being bored is the correct answer
傷は癒えぬまま いたいわ
I want the wounds to remain unhealed
消えちゃって なぁ まざらし見て見ぬふり
Just disappear, hey, pretending not to see it clearly
帰る場所はどこだったっけ まっさらで
Where was the place to return to? It was brand new
傷一つね 囲んで 今を いじれ
Surrounding a single wound, mess with the present
あっちでも前でも 付け足ら選べた 嗤いしちゃ 落ち着かないでしょ
There or in front, if I added it I could choose, you can't settle down if you're sneering, right?
たまさか 苦境を 表現する すっぱ多は 編み出した全部
By chance, expressing the hardship, the acidity has woven everything together
具体的な 未来は バーガー この傷跡 疼かせて ディダース
The concrete future is a burger, making this scar throb, didas
大したことないと思うなら 受け止めて ホラ 勇気ない
If you think it's no big deal, then take it, look, you have no courage
くだらないって 笑って 惑わせて
Call it worthless, laugh, and lead me astray
有象無象 風に吹かれ 目に打たれ Fade out
The masses blown by the wind, struck in the eyes, Fade out
今日と明日を 描いて
Drawing today and tomorrow
焦がれたって 始まりね 火を灯せ
Even if I've yearned for it, it's a beginning, light the fire
Hello, Hello 差し舞って 疑って お好きの
Hello, Hello, offer a dance, doubt it, just as you like
Trust me... Hook up baby
どうしたいって 想い 飽きたさ 差し伸べないで
I'm tired of wondering what I want to do, don't reach out
抱いて揺れ 甘えちゃうわ
Holding me and swaying, I'll end up being spoiled
さらば かつての自分よ あなたを縛る時代よ
Farewell to my former self, to the era that bound you
I don't care, so don't care この旅路へ
I don't care, so don't care on this journey
くだらないって 笑って 惑わせて
Call it worthless, laugh, and lead me astray
有象無象 風に吹かれ 目に打たれ Fade out
The masses blown by the wind, struck in the eyes, Fade out
今日と明日を 描いて
Drawing today and tomorrow
焦がれたって 始まりね 火を灯せ
Even if I've yearned for it, it's a beginning, light the fire
Hello, Hello 差し舞って 疑って お好きの
Hello, Hello, offer a dance, doubt it, just as you like
Trust me... Hook up baby
Chewy Chew, Chewy Chew
Mogu mogu mogu Chewy Chew, Chewy Chew
手を合わせ何度も カッ飛ばしてしまった迷路
Joining hands, time and again, I've dashed through the maze
この道はどこへ続いているのだろう？
Where is this road leading to?
目の前に
Before my eyes
無数に
Countless
別れた
branched
可能性が広がっている。
possibilities are spreading.
ワタシは、私であるために
I, in order to be myself
自分を縛る言葉は捨てて、
will discard the words that bind me,
広がっていくのは
what spreads out is
私だけの、まだ知らない光。
my own, yet unknown light.
10.29 ARIAKE ARENA
Tokoyami Towa 2nd Live SHINIER
進め。輝き溢れる、光の先へ。
Advance. Towards the brilliance-overflowing light.
はい。
Yes.
皆さん、なんと、えー、常闇トワのセカンドソロライブが、
Everyone, believe it or not, Tokoyami Towa's 2nd solo live...
決定しましたー！
...has been confirmed!
イエーイ！うおら！来たぞ！
Yay! Wooh! It's here!
ついに公開された！
It's finally been revealed!
良かったー！
I'm so glad!
ここまでいたったんですけど、まだここが始まりなんだけど、
I've made it this far, but this is still just the beginning,
頑張りますからね。
so I'll do my best.
どうです？びっくりしました？
How was it? Were you surprised?
ありがとう、ありがとうございます。
Thank you, thank you very much.
泣きそう、わかる。
You look like you're gonna cry? I get it.
ちょっと泣きそうなのわかりますわ、一緒。
I understand feeling a bit teary-eyed, same here.
でも、取っておきましょう、それは皆。
But let's save those tears, everyone.
今じゃないわ。
Now isn't the time.
取っておこう。本番までに。
Let's save them for the actual show.
えー、ということで。
Alright, so.
今回のね、ライブタイトルは、常闇トワセカンドライブ『SHINIER』
The title for this live performance is: Tokoyami Towa 2nd Live "SHINIER".
SHINierです。
It's SHINier.
えー こちらなんですが、さっき発売…発表したアルバムのねタイトル「scene」に繋がってるんですよね。
Well, this title is connected to the album titled "scene" that was just... announced.
このね、アルバムなんですけれども色々な「scene」が入ってるアルバムとなってまして、
This album is one that contains many different "scenes,"
その「scene」に沿って今回のライブタイトルも「SHINier」というふうに付けさせていただきました。
and in line with those "scenes," I've named this live concert "SHINier."
1stライブの「Over the we」よりも、もっと輝いて、かっこいい
Even more than my 1st live "Over the we," I'll be shining, looking cool,
無限大の可能性を皆さんにお届けするので、ぜひ見に来てくれればなと思います。
and showing you all infinite possibilities, so I really hope you'll come to see it.
はい！そしてキービジュアル見てみましょう！
Alright! Now, let's take a look at the key visual!
はい！どうですか？
Yes! How is it?
こちらね、アルバムのジャケット写真描いていただいたはなぶしさんにね、キービジュアルも一緒に描いていただきました！
The key visual was also drawn by Hanabushi-san, who did the album cover art!
めっちゃかっこいいよね！
It's so cool, right?
さっきのはちょっと黒い暗い感じだったんだけど、
The previous one had a bit of a dark, black feeling,
こっちはね、光がね見えるような感じで、進んでいくような、前に行けるような明るさを演出してもらいましたね。
but for this one, I had them create a brightness where you can see the light, like moving forward.
すごいもう、クールでかっこいいけど…みたいな感じを出せればと思っております。衣装もお気に入りです！
I hope it conveys a sense of being cool and awesome. I love the outfit too!
当日楽しみです！
I'm looking forward to the big day!
え、そして、今回のハッシュタグは、ライブ、アルバムどちらも共通で、
And the hashtag for this time, common to both the live and the album,
ハッシュタグ シャープ 常山…
is # Tokoyama...
常闇！自分の名前噛むってすごくない？
Tokoyami! Isn't it amazing that I messed up my own name?
今なんかスタッフさんにめっちゃ見られて笑ってんだけど。恥ずかしいんだけど！
The staff are all looking at me and laughing. This is so embarrassing!
えー #常闇トワ2nd です。もう帰りたい！
It's #TokoyamiTowa2nd. I wanna go home now!
ねえ 笑いすぎだから！
Hey, you guys are laughing too much!
え、じゃあ今日から改名して「常山」になります。よろしくお願いいたします。
Okay, from today, I'm changing my name to "Tokoyama." Nice to meet you.
え、皆さんいっぱいポストしてくれればなと思います。
I hope you all post a lot with the hashtag.
はい！そして、皆様お待たせ、チケット情報です！
Alright! And the moment you've been waiting for: ticket information!
本当に耳赤くなるんだけど。
My ears are actually turning red.
会場はなんと！え、有明アリーナです！
The venue is... Ariake Arena!
はい！えー 前回よりもね、もう すごいな、3倍？2.5倍くらいね、会場も広くなって、
Yes! The venue is much larger than last time, like three times or 2.5 times bigger.
前回あんなに緊張して最初震えてたのに、だ、だ、だい、大丈夫かなっていう心配で、
I was so nervous and shaking at the start last time, so I'm worried if I'll be okay.
あの、全然実感湧かなかったんですけど、この今この配信してちょっと実感が湧いてきてプルプルしてきました。
I didn't really feel it before, but doing this stream now, it's starting to sink in and I'm shaking.
ドキドキしてます。でも頑張ります！え、チケットはSS席、S席、A席、B席の4種類です。
My heart is racing, but I'll do my best! There are four types of tickets: SS, S, A, and B seats.
え、こちらのSS席が気になってると思うんですけれども、SS席というのは「SHINier Supporter」の略で、
I'm sure you're curious about the SS seats. SS stands for "SHINier Supporter."
SHINierはトワのことで、そのサポーターは皆様のことなんですよね！
SHINier is me, Towa, and the supporters are all of you!
はい！そしてね、SS席には特典でブレスレットライトがついてきます！
Yes! And SS seats come with a special bonus: a bracelet light!
ちょっとお高いかもしれないんですけども、この席とかねブレスレットライトがついてくる点を考えると、
It might be a bit pricey, but considering the seat and the bracelet light bonus,
もう、目の前で爆音で聴いてほしいなっていう感じなんですけどもね。
I really want you to experience it right in front of the stage with the loud sound.
このブレスレットライト、すごい作りたかったものなので作れて本当に嬉しいです。
I've always wanted to make this bracelet light, so I'm really happy we could do it.
ライブロゴやねタイトルが入ってる特別仕様で、紫色の中、紫色の留め具がマグネットになっていて、
It's a special design with the live logo and title. The purple clasp is a magnet,
付け外しができるようになっております。点灯カラーは白色になっておりまして、
making it easy to put on and take off. The light color is white,
SS席のサポーターの皆様はこれで会場全体をキービジュアルみたいに光り輝かせていただければなと思います！
and I hope all the SS seat supporters will make the venue shine just like the key visual with these!
あの、すっごいいっぱいあるからさ、あの 頑張ってんの今。
There's so much information to share, so I'm doing my best here.
え、じゃあね、気になる各座席のエリアマップ見てみましょう！どんなもんじゃいということで、はい！
Now, let's look at the seat map to see where each area is! Here it is!
そうなんです！SS席はなんとステージのど真ん中にあります！
That's right! The SS seats are located right in the center of the stage!
で、そこの周りをS席、A席、B席というふうに周りを囲んでる形ですね。
And the S, A, and B seats are arranged surrounding that center area.
現地チケットはこの後21時から1次抽選の申し込みが始まるので、みんなぜひ応募してください！
Applications for the first ticket lottery start today at 9:00 PM, so please apply!
え、海外の皆様も買えますのでよろしくお願いします。Overseas bro, sis,
Overseas fans can also purchase tickets. Overseas brothers and sisters,
everyone, let's buy, let's go, let's go! はい！
everyone, let's buy, let's go, let's go! Yes!
というわけで、でも現地に行けないよって人も大丈夫！
So, even if you can't come to the venue, don't worry!
配信チケットもあります！こちらもね21時から発売開始なので特設サイトをチェックしてみてください！
Streaming tickets are also available! Sales start at 9:00 PM, so please check the special site!
概要欄にも更新してくれてると思うんですけど、リンクがありますので、あるけど…
The link should be in the video description, it's there, but...
あるけどね、「常闇トワ 2ndライブ」で検索してもサイトで出てくるので、ブックマークしておくといいかもしれません。
even if it's there, you can find the site by searching for "Tokoyami Towa 2nd Live," so bookmarking it might be a good idea.
ちょっと出るか検索してみて。ちょっと心配だから。はい！
Try searching and see if it comes up. I'm a bit worried. Yes!
配信でもね、現地でも、どちらもかっこいいね、みんなが喜べる、喜んでくれるようなパフォーマンスを頑張ってしたいと思うので、
Whether you're watching online or at the venue, I'll do my best to give a cool performance that will make everyone happy.
最後まで頑張って走り抜けたいと思います。
I want to do my best and run through to the end.
はい、そしてここまであっという間だったんですが、
Yes, and it's been a blur so far,
今回のライブ情報はここまでになります。
but that's all for the information about this live.
あれ？なんかライブに必要なものが足りなくない？
Wait, isn't something necessary for a live missing?
って思ったそこの眷属ー！
You over there, my Kenzoku!
すごいカメラがね大変だったんで、あんまり動かないようにしますけども。
The camera was having a hard time, so I'll try not to move too much.
ライブグッズは現在準備中になります。
The live goods are currently being prepared.
え、またね別の日にライブグッズを発表する枠も取りたいと思いますから、
I'll also set up another stream on a different day to announce the live goods,
お楽しみに待っててください。
so please look forward to it.
貯金のタイムだから。いい？皆さん貯金タイム。
It's saving time. Got it? Everyone, save up.
と思いきや、ここまでがライブの告知。
Or so I thought, that's it for the live announcements.
で、貯金タイムって言ったんだけど、ここからは貯金しないでほしいタイムです。
And I said it's saving time, but from here on out, it's "please don't save" time.
え、常闇トワ誕生日記念2025のグッズ発売告知となります！
The announcement for the release of Tokoyami Towa Birthday Commemoration 2025 goods!
ぼー見てください。こちら。
Look at this!
常闇トワ 誕生記念 2025
Tokoyami Towa Birthday Commemoration 2025
イエーイ！rurudoマミーにイラスト描いてもらっちゃいました。
Yay! I had rurudo-mommy draw the illustration for me.
マミーありがとう！かわいいよね。
Thank you, Mommy! It's cute, isn't it?
はい、え、詳細をねみんなで見ていこうと思います。こちら。
Yes, let's take a look at the details together. Here.
B2タペストリー / イラスト：rurudo
B2 Tapestry / Illustration: rurudo
じゃじゃん。そうこれマミーに描いてもらった、え、ゴシックな部屋の撮影のトワちゃん。
Tada! Yes, this is Towa-chan in a gothic room, drawn by Mommy.
で、ちょっとrurudoマミーの若干性癖がどこかに詰まってるんで、どこか当ててくださいね。
And rurudo-mommy's slight fetishes are packed in there somewhere, so please try to guess where.
ビッグタオル / イラスト：Mr.Lime
Big Towel / Illustration: Mr.Lime
はい、そしてこちらビッグタオル！Mr.Lime先生に描いてくれ、いただき、いただきました。
Yes, and here is the Big Towel! Drawn by Mr.Lime-sensei.
Lime先生いつもありがとう。このね、配信のサムネも描いてくれました。
Thank you as always, Lime-sensei. He also drew the thumbnail for this stream.
ありがとう、いつも。昔からずっと描いてくださってる先生です。
Thank you, as always. He's been drawing for me for a long time.
はい、こちらもビッグサイズのタオルぜひ使ってくれればなと思います。
Yes, this is also a big-sized towel, so I hope you'll use it.
続いてはこちら。ポン！
Next is this. Pop!
トワ様とお出かけぬいぐるみキーホルダー
Towa-sama and Outing Plushie Keychain
トワ様とお出かけぬいぐるみキーホルダー！
The "Towa-sama and Outing Plushie Keychain"!
これはですねやっぱトワちゃんね、あの結構毎月トワベルっていうので
For this, as you know, I have the "TowaBelle" streams every month
みんながトワのぬいぐるみと一緒に結構旅行してくれてそれをあの、行った気持ちになる配信があるんですけども。
where everyone travels with my plushie and I feel like I'm traveling too.
やっぱ私服でねちょっとま、デートというか、まあデートとしてやっていい。
Since it's in plain clothes, you can use it for a date, well, a date is fine too.
っていう意味を込めて私服のミニチュアサイズというかもう持ち運びできるような、お出かけぬいぐるみキーホルダーを作らせていただきましたんで、
With that in mind, I made this miniature-sized, portable plushie keychain in plain clothes.
また買って届いたらいっぱいね、投稿してくれればなと思います。
I hope you'll buy it and post lots of photos when it arrives.
はい、そしてこちら。
Yes, and here.
眷属メタルキーホルダー
Kenzoku Metal Keychain
眷属メタルキーホルダー！
Kenzoku Metal Keychain!
え、かわいいビビと、あとはトワやっぱねえ歌ももちろん大好きなんですけども。
It's got cute Bibi and, as you know, I love singing, of course.
ゲームもやっぱりすごい好き。
But I also really love games.
なんで、えーそのねイメージをこちらに詰め込んでいただけました。かわいいでしょ、キーホルダー。
So, those themes are packed into this. It's cute, isn't it, this keychain?
最近トワね、いろんなところにキーホルダーをジャラジャラつけるのにはまってるんで、
Lately, I've been into hanging lots of keychains on everything,
作ってみました。よろしくお願いいたします。
so I made this. Thank you.
フルセットの、えー購入特典もございますので見てみましょう。
There's also a purchase bonus for the full set, so let's take a look.
フルセット購入特典 / 箔押し複製サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカード
Full Set Purchase Bonus / Cheki-style bromide card with foil-stamped duplicated signature
はい、rurudoマミーのちょっとペロッみたいな表情差分があるトワちゃんの、
Yes, it comes with a Cheki-style bromide card with rurudo-mommy's illustration of Towa-chan with a "blep" expression difference
え、箔製、箔製じゃねえわ、箔押し複製サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードがついてきます！
and a foil-stamped duplicated signature!
はい、フルセット買うとついてくるんだよ、これが。でもね、そしてね、しかもね、
Yes, you get this if you buy the full set. But wait, there's more!
なんと、もう一個ついてきちゃうの。こちら。
What's more, you get one more thing. This.
戻ってね。あ、これだった、あ、ごめん。あ、あれこれか。フルセットはこれ。
Going back. Oh, it was this, oh, sorry. Is it this? This is the full set.
はい、これ。12345、これでこれがついてきて、でこれ。これがついてくる。次。
Yes, this. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5. With this, you get this, and then this. You get this. Next.
hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME / PRカード BBD24-062 「常闇トワ」
hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME / PR Card BBD24-062 "Tokoyami Towa"
これこれこれこれ。もうオートバッシュしながら、これ。
This, this, this, this! While doing an auto-bash, this!
これがついてきます。え、カードがねついてきますよ。hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAMEで使用できるカードが1枚ついてきぱーと。
This is included. Yes, a card is included. One card that can be used in the hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME is included.
え、カードはねホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルショップで購入された方のみ対象となっております。
The card is only for those who purchase from the Hololive Production Official Shop.
特典につくのは推しアピールできるキーカード、推しホロメンカードです。
The bonus is an "Oshi Holomen Card", a key card to show off your favorite.
カードの詳細や遊び方についてはホームページで確認してくれい。
Please check the website for details on the card and how to play.
ということで以上、常闇トワ誕生日記念グッズの情報でした。
So, that was the information about Tokoyami Towa's Birthday Commemoration goods.
みんな買ってね。これで素敵なMV作るんだから、買ってくれないといいの作れないから（笑）よろしくね。
Everyone, please buy them. I'm going to make a great MV with this, so if you don't buy them, I won't be able to make something good (laughs). Thank you.
はい、そしてそして先ほどお伝えしたセカンドアルバム「SHIN」がホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルショップでの発売が先行して開始しております！
Yes, and, and, as I mentioned earlier, pre-orders for my second album "SHIN" have started on the Hololive Production Official Shop!
Tokoyami Towa 2nd Album SHIN
はい、多分あの配信画面の下に出てきた購入ボタンから発売ページに飛べるようになってると思うんですけども、皆さん、お知りになりました？
Yes, I think you can go to the sales page from the purchase button that appeared below the stream screen, but did you all notice?
しら、あの、もしなかったらね更新でお願いいたします。更新してください。
If, well, if not, please refresh. Please refresh.
はい、え購入ボタンをクリックする前に注意事項なのですが、セカンドアルバムとそれ以外のものを同じカードで購入していただいた場合に、
Yes, a point of caution before clicking the purchase button: if you purchase the second album and other items in the same cart,
え発売日の10月8日までに発送が行われない可能性があるので気をつけてください。
there's a possibility they won't be shipped by the release date of October 8th, so please be careful.
セカンドアルバム単体での購入なら大丈夫です。ありがとう。買ったありがとうありがとうね。
If you purchase the second album by itself, it's fine. Thank you. Thank you for buying, thank you.
ありがとう。ホロライブ公式以外でのご購入...
Thank you. For purchases outside of the official Hololive channel...
まあこのあと9時からになりますからね。
Well, it'll start at 9 PM after this.
ありがとう、もう買ってくれてありがとう！
Thank you! Thanks for already buying it!
はい、そしてもうあと少し！
Yes! And just a little more!
このあと8時50分、チュウチュウビのMVプレミア公開がありまして、
At 8:50 PM after this, the MV for 'Chu-Chu-Bi' will premiere...
9時からライブチケットの発売がございます！
...and from 9 PM, live concert tickets will be on sale!
ということで今日は1時間枠じゃなくて、ちょっと短いんですけど、
So, today wasn't a full hour slot, it was a bit short...
こんな感じでまた後日配信すると思うので、
...but I think I'll stream again another day like this...
ぜひまた遊びに来てください！
...so please come visit again!
はい、では皆さん、このあとチュウチュウビ、
Alright then everyone, next is 'Chu-Chu-Bi'.
ここにいたらすぐ聴けるんで、かっこいいMV聴けるんで、
If you stay here you can hear it right away, the cool MV.
ここに待機してしばし待たれよ！
So stay right here and wait for a bit!
ということで、今日はありがとう！
So, thank you for today!
いっぱいポストしてね！
Post lots of tweets!
駆け足になっちゃった、またねー！
I've got to run, see ya!
常闇トワ 生誕祭 2025
Sincerely, Towa
重大発表あり
2025.8.8 20:00 Start
Tokoyami Towa Birthday Festival 2025
Sincerely, Towa
Major Announcement Included
2025.8.8 20:00 Start